<feed>
	<doc>
		<title>Anarchy</title>
		<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anarchy</url>
		<abstract>
			Anarchy is the condition of a society, entity, group of people, or a single person that rejects hierarchy.[1] The word originally meant leaderlessness, but in 1840 Pierre-Joseph Proudhon adopted the term in his treatise What Is Property? to refer to a new political philosophy: anarchism, which advocates stateless societies based on voluntary associations. In practical terms, anarchy can refer to the curtailment or abolition of traditional forms of government and institutions. It can also designate a nation (or anywhere on earth that is inhabited) that has no system of government or central rule.
		</abstract>
		<links>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anarchy#Etymology</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anarchy#Political_philosophy</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anarchy#Anthropology</link></sublink>
		</links>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<title>Abraham Lincoln</title>
		<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abraham_Lincoln</url>
		<abstract>
			Abraham Lincoln (February 12, 1809 – April 15, 1865) was an American statesman and lawyer who served as the 16th President of the United States from March 1861 until his assassination in April 1865. Lincoln led the United States through its Civil War—its bloodiest war and perhaps its greatest moral, constitutional, and political crisis.[2][3] In doing so, he preserved the Union, paved the way to the abolition of slavery, strengthened the federal government, and modernized the economy.

Born in Hodgenville, Kentucky, Lincoln grew up on the western frontier in Kentucky and Indiana. Largely self-educated, he became a lawyer in Illinois, a Whig Party leader, and was elected to the Illinois House of Representatives, in which he served for eight years. Elected to the United States House of Representatives in 1846, Lincoln promoted rapid modernization of the economy and opposed the Mexican–American War. After a single term, he returned to Illinois and resumed his successful law practice. Reentering politics in 1854, he became a leader in building the new Republican Party, which had a statewide majority in Illinois. As part of the 1858 campaign for US Senator from Illinois, Lincoln took part in a series of highly publicized debates with his opponent and rival, Democrat Stephen A. Douglas; Lincoln spoke out against the expansion of slavery, but lost the race to Douglas. In 1860, Lincoln secured the Republican Party presidential nomination as a moderate from a swing state, though most delegates originally favored other candidates. Though he gained very little support in the slaveholding states of the South, he swept the North and was elected president in 1860.
		</abstract>
		<links>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anarchy#Etymology</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anarchy#Political_philosophy</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anarchy#Anthropology</link></sublink>
		</links>
	</doc>

	<doc>
		<title>Pizza</title>
		<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza</url>
		<abstract>
			Pizza is a yeasted flatbread typically topped with tomato sauce and cheese and baked in an oven. It is commonly topped with a selection of meats, vegetables and condiments.

The term pizza was first recorded in the 10th century, in a Latin manuscript from Gaeta in Central Italy.[1] Modern pizza was invented in Naples, Italy, and the dish and its variants have since become popular and common in many areas of the world.[2] In 2009, upon Italy's request, Neapolitan pizza was safeguarded in the European Union as a Traditional Speciality Guaranteed dish.[3][4] Associazione Verace Pizza Napoletana (True Neapolitan Pizza Association), a non-profit organization founded in 1984 with headquarters in Naples, aims to "promote and protect... the true Neapolitan pizza".[5]

Pizza is sold fresh or frozen, either whole or in portions, and is a common fast food item in Europe and North America.[6] Various types of ovens are used to cook them and many varieties exist. Several similar dishes are prepared from ingredients commonly used in pizza preparation, such as calzone and stromboli.
		</abstract>
		<links>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#History</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#Preparation</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#Varieties</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#Records</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#Health_issues</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#National_Pizza_Month</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#Similar_dishes</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#See_also</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#References</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#Further_reading</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza#External_links</link></sublink>
			
		</links>
	</doc>

	<doc>
		<title>Pizza Delivery</title>
		<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery</url>
		<abstract>
			Pizza delivery is a service in which a pizzeria or pizza chain delivers a pizza to a customer. An order is typically made either by telephone or over the internet to the pizza chain, in which the customer can request pizza type, size and other products alongside the pizza, commonly including soft drinks. Pizzas may be delivered in pizza boxes or delivery bags, and deliveries are made with either an automobile, motorized scooter, or bicycle. Customers can, depending on the pizza chain, choose to pay online, or in person, with cash, credit or a debit card. A delivery fee is often charged with what the customer has bought.
		</abstract>
		<links>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#Ordering</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#Charge</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#Delivery_technology</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#Employment</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#Hazards</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>hhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#In_popular_culture</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#See_also</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#References</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_delivery#External_links</link></sublink>
		</links>
	</doc>

	<doc>
		<title>The Wedge (Australian TV series)</title>
		<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)</url>
		<abstract>
			The Wedge was an Australian sketch show created by Ian McFadyen and produced by Network Ten, largely based around autobiographical events from the life of the executive producer, Christina Adams. The show stars Dailan Evans, from the ABC sketch show Eagle and Evans; Adam Zwar, best known for his roles in Wilfred, Rebel Wilson, 'Toula' on the comedy show Pizza; Jason Gann, two-time winner of best actor at Tropfest for his roles in Wilfred, as well as regulars Kate Jenkinson, Anthony Ahern, Katrina Mathers, Julie Eckersley and Ross Daniels. Marney McQueen, Aidan Fennesy and Cori Hooper were also regulars in Series 1, and Damian Callinan and Cal Wilson were regulars in Series 2.

It ran for two seasons, airing 2006 and 2007. A spin-off mockumentary of one of the show's characters, Mark Wary, was produced by Network Ten in 2008. The show, titled Mark Loves Sharon premiered at 9:30pm on 30 June 2008.
		</abstract>
		<links>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#History_and_premise</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#Cast_and_crew</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#Characters_and_sketches</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#DVD_releases</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#Episode_guide</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#Critical_reception</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#Side_projects</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#References</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wedge_(Australian_TV_series)#External_links</link></sublink>
		</links>
	</doc>

	<doc>
		<title>Pizza cheese</title>
		<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese</url>
		<abstract>
			Pizza cheese encompasses several varieties and types of cheeses and dairy products that are designed and manufactured for use specifically on pizza. These include processed and modified cheese such as mozzarella-like processed cheeses and mozzarella variants. The term can also refer to any type of cheese suitable for use on pizza.[1] The most popular cheeses used in the preparation of pizza are mozzarella (accounting for about 30%), provolone, cheddar and Parmesan. Emmental, Romano and ricotta are often used as toppings, and processed pizza cheeses manufactured specifically for pizza are mass-produced.[2] Some mass-produced pizza cheeses are frozen after manufacturing and shipped frozen.

Processed pizza cheese is manufactured to produce optimal qualities in browning, melting, stretchiness and fat and moisture content. Several studies and experiments have analyzed the impact of vegetable oil, manufacturing and culture processes,[3] denatured whey proteins[4][5] and other changes to create ideal and economical pizza cheeses.[6] In 1997, it was estimated that annual production of pizza cheese products was 2 billion pounds in the United States and 200 million pounds in Europe, and in 2000 demand for the product in Europe was increasing by 8% per year. The trend of steadily-increasing production and consumption of mozzarella and pizza cheese continued into the first decade of the 21st century in the United States.[7]
		</abstract>
		<links>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#Varieties_and_types</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#Research_and_development</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#Production_and_business</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#Use_by_region</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#See_also</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#Notes</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#References</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#Further_reading</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_cheese#External_links</link></sublink>
		</links>
	</doc>

	<doc>
		<title>Pizza Hut</title>
		<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut</url>
		<abstract>
			Pizza Hut is an American restaurant chain and international franchise founded in 1958 by Dan and Frank Carney. The company is known for its Italian-American cuisine menu including pizza and pasta, as well as side dishes and desserts. Pizza Hut has over 16,000 locations worldwide as of 2015, and is a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc., one of the world's largest restaurant companies.
		</abstract>
		<links>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#History</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#Concept</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#Products</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#Advertising</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#Criticism</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#See_also</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#References</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#Further_reading</link></sublink>
			<sublink><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pizza_Hut#External_links</link></sublink>
		</links>
	</doc>




















</feed>
